[
    {
        "question": "What is 23 - 7?",
        "answer": "16",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 37 - 12?",
        "answer": "25",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 48 - 18?",
        "answer": "30",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 55 - 17?",
        "answer": "38",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 34 - 9?",
        "answer": "25",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 29 - 14?",
        "answer": "15",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 42 - 19?",
        "answer": "23",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 39 - 26?",
        "answer": "13",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 33 - 11?",
        "answer": "22",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 27 - 15?",
        "answer": "12",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    }
]
